{
  "topic": "6.2",
  "title": "Уравнения с корнем",
  "types": [
    {
      "id": "6.2.1",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{9x - 47} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 },
          "unic": true
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{3x + 34} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{2x + 28} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{5x + 49} = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{4x + 17} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{7x + 8} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{6x + 19} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{3x + 57} = 9 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{2x + 50} = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{5x + 51} = 9 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{4x + 36} = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{3x + 19} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{2x + 31} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{7x + 4} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{6x + 12} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{5x + 24} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{4x + 25} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{3x + 43} = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{2x + 13} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.1.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{5x + 16} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "6.2.2",
      "title": "",
      "prototypes": [
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.1",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{99 - 7x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.2",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{45 - 5x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.3",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{67 - 3x} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.4",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{56 - 4x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.5",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{39 - 2x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.6",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{67 - 6x} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.7",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{64 - 7x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.8",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{26 - 5x} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 2 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.9",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{51 - 3x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.10",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{57 - 2x} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.11",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{37 - 4x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 3 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.12",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{94 - 6x} = 8 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 5 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.13",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{67 - 7x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.14",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{71 - 5x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.15",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{49 - 3x} = 5 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.16",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{54 - 2x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 9 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.17",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{81 - 4x} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 8 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.18",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{78 - 6x} = 6 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 7 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.19",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{79 - 5x} = 7 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 6 }
        },
        {
          "id": "6.2.2.20",
          "stem": "Найдите корень уравнения\n\n\\[ \\Large \\sqrt{28 - 3x} = 4 \\]\n\n",
          "answer": { "value": 4 }
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
